Hi, my name is David Brown and this is a reading writing class.
大家好，我叫戴维·布朗，这是一堂读写课。
Persuasive in your communication be useful for you, your studies, your future
在你的沟通中具有说服力，将对你本人、你的学业、你未来的
career, and etc.
职业生涯等等都有用。
Being more persuasive in your communication be useful for you.
在沟通中更具说服力会对你有所帮助。
To be more persuasive means to be able to get other people to do what you want.
更具说服力意味着能够让别人做你希望他们做的事情。
To do what you want, exactly.
做你希望他们做的事，完全正确。
How to be more persuasive?
如何才能更具说服力呢？
Well, you have to learn, they say, once I heard, once you know the crowd you are talking to,
嗯，你必须学习，他们说，我曾经听说，一旦你了解了你谈话的对象，
you have to learn how to talk the same way they talk so they can understand you better.
你就必须学习如何用他们说话的方式来说话，这样他们才能更好地理解你。
But at the same time, with their same words, with the same way they talk,
但同时，用他们同样的词语，用他们同样的说话方式，
you have to teach them something.
你必须教给他们一些东西。
And once you teach, they can be able to follow you.
一旦你进行了教导，他们就能够跟随你。
I think everyone has something that they can persuade us of if they just have the ability
我认为每个人都有一些可以用来来说服我们的东西，只要他们有这个能力，
to do that, those communication skills to talk and express themselves well.
那些能够很好地交谈和表达自己的沟通技巧。
It's not easy.
这不容易。
No, it's not easy, I agree.
不，这不容易，我同意。
It can be difficult.
这可能很难。
And this is something that we can improve.
这是我们可以改进的地方。
We can learn how to be more persuasive in our communication.
我们可以学习如何在沟通中更具说服力。
And something that Frederick Douglass teaches us about, if you read his autobiography and we'll
弗雷德里克·道格拉斯 (Fúléidélǐkè Dàogélāsī) 教会了我们一些关于说服力的重要理念，如果你读他的自传，我们今天会
read a section of it today, you'll notice just how persuasive he is.
读其中的一部分，你就会注意到他是多么有说服力。
He's just a really good writer, a really great persuasive writer for this cause.
他确实是一位非常优秀的作家，一位为这项事业 (shìyè) 写作的、极具说服力的伟大作家。
And his words made a big impact because he was so persuasive.
他的话语之所以能产生巨大影响，正是因为他非常有说服力。
So recap here, who was Frederick Douglass exactly?
那么，回顾一下，弗雷德里克·道格拉斯究竟是谁？
You can see a collage of images here.
你可以在这里看到一组图片拼贴。
This is from the pre-civil war, civil war era.
这是来自内战前和内战时期的。
You can see other examples of abolitionists in this photo here.
你可以在这张照片中看到其他废奴主义者 (fèinú zhǔyì zhě) 的例子。
So he was born in 1818 and died in 1895.
他生于1818年，卒于1895年。
Of his prime was during the Civil War, he was an African-American social reformer, abolitionist,
他的鼎盛时期是在内战期间，他是一位非裔美国社会改革家、废奴主义者、
or writer, writer, and statesman.
演说家 (yǎnshuōjiā)、作家和政治家。
Can you read this part for us here?
可以请您帮我们读一下这部分吗？
After escaping from slavery in Maryland, he became a national leader of the abolitionist movement.
在从马里兰州的奴隶生活中逃脱后，他成为了废奴运动的全国领袖。
Famous for his powerful speeches and writings?
以其强有力的演讲和著述闻名？
Excellent. In fact, Abraham Lincoln knew about this man and had read his writings.
非常好。事实上，亚伯拉罕·林肯也知道这个人，并读过他的著作。
And it was some of his writings that inspired him to go along with this movement.
正是他的部分著作激励了林肯参与到这场运动中来。
So we have a chart here.
我们这里有一个图表。
We're going to think about what we know already about Frederick Douglass,
我们将思考一下关于弗雷德里克·道格拉斯我们已经了解了什么，
maybe what I've told you already, or what you've heard before, or what you know about the
可能是我已经告诉过你的，或者你以前听说过的，或者你对
Civil War already. What do you know already about this abolitionist or the Civil War?
内战已经了解的内容。关于这位废奴主义者或内战，你已经知道了什么？
From what you told me, well, he is an African-American, a slave.
根据您告诉我的，嗯，他是一位非裔美国人，一个奴隶。
He learned to read from others.
他从别人那里学会了阅读。
He wasn't taught how to read, but he learned from hearing other people how to read, right?
他没被教过阅读，是靠听别人读书学会的，对吗？
And he died of 77 years old, and he escaped from slavery in Maryland.
他去世时77岁，并且从马里兰州的奴隶生活中逃脱了。
And once he learned how to read, he was a famous .
一旦他学会了阅读，他就成了一位著名的 。
He was a famous writer.
他是一位著名的作家。
Writer. Famous abolitionist and writer. Excellent.
作家。著名的废奴主义者和作家。非常好。
You're a good listener. Thank you.
你听得很仔细。谢谢。
Now, there are new things to learn here. What questions do you have about Frederick Douglass?
现在，这里有一些新的东西需要学习。关于弗雷德里克·道格拉斯，你有什么问题吗？
What kind of things would you like to know about him?
你想了解他的哪些方面？
Oh.
哦。
Okay, it says that he escaped from slavery. Why did he do after that?
好的，上面说他从奴隶生活中逃脱了。那之后他做了什么？
Yeah.
是的。
And how do you think you'll find out? Well, I think we can find out through today's lessons and
你认为你会怎么找到答案呢？嗯，我想我们可以通过今天的课程和活动来找到答案，
activities, but actually what we're going to read today has more to do with his thoughts before
但实际上我们今天要读的内容更多是关于他逃跑之前的想法。
he escaped. I still think you can have some idea about what he had to do or what led him to
我仍然认为你可以对他当时必须做什么，或者是什么促使他能够逃脱有一些了解。
being able to escape. And this is something else that maybe you'll be able to
这也是一些你或许能够在今天这堂课之后
read after this lesson today as well if you'd like to finish reading his autobiography.
如果你想读完他的自传的话，可以读到的其他内容。
And some of his writings. So we have some vocabulary that we need to focus on. We'll read a passage
以及他的一些著作。我们有一些需要重点掌握的词汇。我们将阅读一段弗雷德里克·道格拉斯自传中的
from Frederick Douglass's autobiography where he describes his determination to learn to read
段落，他在其中描述了自己学习读写的决心。
and write. Nothing could stop this guy. He did everything he could to educate himself in
没有什么能阻止这个人。他尽其所能地教育自己，
a world in which it was very taboo for a slave to learn to read and write.
在一个奴隶学习读写被视为非常禁忌的世界里。
Okay. These are some vocabulary words that we need to know here. I'd like for you to take a look
好的。这些是我们在这里需要了解的一些词汇。我希望你看看这些词
at these and their definitions. We have strategies. Can you read the definition for me here?
以及它们的定义。我们有 "strategies" (策略 cèlüè)。你能为我读一下这里的定义吗？
Clever tricks. Clever tricks are plans used to achieve a goal.
巧妙的计策。巧妙的计策或为达到某一目标而使用的计划。
Deprovity.
"Depravity" (道德败坏 dàodé bàihuài)。
I cannot see it out. Moral corruptions or wickedness. Wickedness.
我看不清。道德败坏或邪恶 (xié'è)。邪恶。
About this one. Shuttle. In item of first, how do you pronounce it?
这个呢。"Chattel" (动产 dòngchǎn)。第一个词，这个怎么发音？
Shuttle. Shuttle. It sounds like a French, right?
"Chattel" (chattel)。"Chattel"。听起来像法语，对吧？
An item or personal property. In slave people were legally
一件物品或私有财产。被奴役的人在法律上
considered shuttle. So it's basically like a worthless object. They were treated like just
被视为 "chattel" (动产)。所以基本上就像一件没有价值的物品。他们仅仅被当作
objects, just things that could be used and thrown away. And this one precepts, precepts.
物品，可以被使用然后丢弃的东西来对待。然后这个，"precepts" (准则 zhǔnzé / 戒律 jièlǜ)。"Precepts"。
Rules are principles guiding behavior. Apprehension.
指导行为的规则或原则。"Apprehension" (忧虑 yōulǜ / 理解 lǐjiě)。
You hear me.
你听到了吗。
Apprehension. You hear me? Apprehension.
"Apprehension"。你听到了吗？"Apprehension"。
Fear. Now I can. Fear and anxiety that something bad will happen. Also understanding.
恐惧。现在我听到了。对将要发生坏事的恐惧和焦虑。也指理解。
No. Urchins.
不。"Urchins" (顽童 wántóng / 小淘气鬼 xiǎo tǎoqìguǐ)。
Urchins mischievous. No, I don't know how to pronounce it.
"Urchins" 淘气的。不，我不知道这个怎么发音。
Mischievous. Mischievous.
"Mischievous" (mischievous)。"Mischievous"。
Often poor and regularly closed children.
通常指贫穷且衣衫褴褛的孩子。
They have sea urchins. Sea urchin is the type of sea creature with spikes on it.
有 "sea urchins" (海胆 hǎidǎn)。海胆是一种身上长满刺的海洋生物。
But you can use them to describe children to urchins for good.
但你也可以用 "urchins" 来形容孩子，带有善意的淘气意味。
And this one, vindication. Vindication.
然后这个，"vindication" (证明无辜/正当 zhèngmíng wúgū/zhèngdàng)。"Vindication"。
And vindication. Clearing someone of blame. Oh, and suspicious. Proof that someone or something is
以及 "vindication"。为某人洗清罪名。哦，还有证明。证明某人或某事是
right or reasonable. And a boy. A boy. To regard with disgust and hatred.
正确或合理的证据。然后是 "abhor" (憎恶 zēngwù)。"Abhor"。怀着厌恶和憎恨看待。
And hatred.
和憎恨。
So we use this as a verb to abore something, to really hate something.
所以我们把它用作动词，去 "abhor" 某事物，即非常痛恨某事物。
So a lot of these words really highlight some of the things that we'll talk about through our
这些词汇中的很多都确实突出了我们将在阅读中
reading or read together. When we read, we'll try to focus on the meaning, although I can help you with
一起讨论的一些内容。当我们阅读时，我们会尽量关注意义，尽管我可以帮助你发音，
pronunciation. I don't want it to.
但我不想让它（发音）成为障碍。